Yes then, I would like to begin the happiness of either Major Debut Spring Tour 2023!
First of all, I'd like to start with a voice or what is it?
Theme?
I don't know, minced meat...
Ground meat...
LOL!
I'll get to the minced meat part.
Ground meat...
You know, the minced meat manager...
Yesterday you were telling a story about a library.
You were telling a story.
Yes.
Well...
What do you think?
I have a concept of a book or a library or something like that.
So, I'd like to open the book first, before the overtour.
And then we'll open it and play the Overtour.
I was thinking that it would be nice if you could
I thought it would be a good idea to show the start of the Overtour.
It's like a music video.
Like a music video?
Yes, yes, and a little more visible.
A bigger version.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
It's our first major tour, and I was wondering if it was the first song or the second song if it was just for the last week or two.
Ah! It's the same!
I think it's good.
The first song would be fine, but the last song would be a little bit better, don't you think? You think, "Isn't it good?
That kind of gray is a signal, and that's how they got the message.
It's true that it's not the first song.
But if it was the last song, it might be easier to convey the message with a love file,
But if you want, the first song will end with "ahhhh".
There is NG again.
Yes.
I was saying yesterday, if we are going to do the concept of Sora-chan's coming-of-age novel,
I was saying yesterday that if we are going to use Sora-chan's coming-of-age novel as the concept, we should start without a tour and start with a narrative,
And during the story, I put in what everyone else said,
I thought the after-menu of the first song would be good, so I thought the beginning of the after-menu would be good.
That's good.
Like the beginning of a story.
Like a girl arpeggio.
Like an arpeggio.
First of all, I'll start with the songs,
We have six new songs.
Six songs, plus this Mick, so we have seven songs, and then the rest.
In terms of the previous songs, it's good that we can't change them because they have youth in the lyrics.
I remember the old days.
There were quite a few.
Ah, I understand.
Because it has a nice arpeggiated feel to it,
Poichi and Osoorai.
Thanks for your help.
The party of no swoosh and lie, no reverse, no asking, loafers, 214, coach second, 85 minutes...
I thought there was something adolescent about this party.
I've been thinking that "telemonkey" means "youth" and I've been doing it on my own.
Not adolescent?
It was like a classic coming of age.
Personally, I think we should start with three songs.
Maybe we'll start the week with some grapes.
There's so many songs I want to play.
I tried to remember, but I usually write down 20 songs.
So, 22 songs, two hours.
I'm doing this live with MC.
MC
About 9 or 16 songs?
Mm-hmm.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve.
December 7th.
19th.
Already done.
Maybe it's already over.
I have to go home for the day.
Can you come back?
Day trip.
I'm lost.
It's not the first half of the trip.
How about the last part if we go back? It's fine.
The second song is about 85 minutes long.
It's in the morning, so it's in the right time zone.
I thought it would be around 7:00 or so.I thought it would be right away or around 7:00.
Second song.
What kind of story is this?
That's what he said,
Aftermoon means it's already afternoon.
That's right.
It's a bit of a contradiction in terms.
But why don't you just run with it?
Turn the page.
But I can still see it.
How should I look at it?
I see the hand with the teeth.
That's right.
I've only been doing the hand of the tooth.
The hand with the teeth is different.
That's what I'm asking you to do, or leave it out.
I'm going to do 85 minutes and change it up every day.
This is something I remember very well.
When Rina called the title.
That's it.
Intersection of 85 minutes.
That's how I remember it.
It's like we do it all the time.
I'm thinking of New Fiction.
I put New Fiction.
So it's not 85 minutes,
I fixed New Fiction.
Fanfare is the second song.
I had Fanfare.
It was great.
It was good.
I said it was like the beginning.
It was like a fanfare.
I understand.
I want you to use my song.
Then put Au's in there, too.
I like Uuno.
You can't tell how sharp it is, can you?
Uno's catchiness.
It's a bright song. It's a song that gets people excited.
Did Uno have a voice?
No.
No?
Koichi says he doesn't have it either.
In 2020.
Just in time.
Self-introduction.
Introductions.
What'll you give me for this?
Four?
How many songs do you want in total?
I've got a lot of songs,
I think it would be faster if you put them together in a puzzle.
I understand.
Everybody
Everybody wanna be
I understand.
It's common, but it's more exciting at the end.
It's not anyone, but....
It's not anyone, but...
I know.
Because, you know.
Do you want to go around? Seriously?
It might all come out.
360 points.
Wings.
I miss it. You haven't put them to bed lately?
I don't know. It's okay.
Kitama.
Boku Yale.
What if I do that?
Please. It says, "Don't be sad.
I won't. Yes, yes.
I'm Reflection.
Aline.
I think we should definitely do one of them, because I think there will be people who are coming for the first time and people who will probably come for the first time to the Glittering Recueil Lindbergh.I think we should definitely do one of the Glittering Slack Lindberghs, since some of them will be coming for the first time and some will probably be coming for the first time.
I forgot. Already soon.
They are a natural.
I'll just do the songs I did for this one,
I'll just substitute.
Recue Lindbergh, Glitter should probably be fixed.
I'm next block, Killer Lips, instead of not changing the color.
I was thinking maybe 100% would work.
Something like that, even for me, I'm opening the MC and I'm getting a lot of images of girl's night.
I know, I know.
I have a lot of images of something like Anten Girls Night.
It's okay to wear something a little more adult-like.
I think we could do with a little more sound around here.
We have a few more blocks to go, so maybe we should change it up a bit in this next movement or so.
We need to decide on the theme for this block.
I guess we'll go with adults next time.
So, why not keep the theme of youth here?
I don't think I can go back here.
I don't think I can go home.
So you can't go back in loafers?
Yeah, I can't.
You said it was your favorite time.
Then we'll go to the next girls' night out.
I think we can get there pretty early.
We've been winding down so far, right?
It's only 10 seconds.
Ten seconds?
Ten seconds.
10 seconds?
Okay, let's move on.
Let's go here.
The daily grating that does about M9 or M10.
Less? Daily change of rating.
I'd like to see a local Love 5 that changes daily.
After wearing a T-shirt.
Maybe just this one, something around here.
11 is Cosnick for now.
Here?
Yeah.
Where do we put the youth clothes?
Uh, this one.
Wait a minute. It's goth-ish.
But you're going to go buy this in the grown-up block?
Yeah.
So, where do you think it's going to be on a daily basis?
And then, you know, we'll have to throw away all these clothes, won't we?
Oh, no!
I want to do it! I want to do it! I want to do it!
Let's do it. Let's do it.
Sorry, friarliga8.
Friar Riga 8.
This is eight.
This is 8.
If I do it now, you know, that's the last of the love lights.
Oh, okay.
Is it the last one?
Last?
But this is the last one, the last one in the love light, and it's over.
It's the last one in the love light, but you can fix it.
How much is the last one? Like...
Like M16 Sparkle.
Oh, glitter.
But on a T-shirt. Here.
Oh, I see.
I was thinking, you know, 12, 13, 14...
Oh, like that.
Like "Ebibuddy," "Wannabe," "Maru Glitter," that kind of thing.
Uh-huh.
Uh...
Kira Lips and Vivana.
That leaves...
Where's Killalips?
Is it weird that it ends with 14 Viva la Viva la Viva la?
No, it's not weird.
I just thought it would be easier to end it with "Viva la" than "Killalips" and then "Love.
You can't read "love".You can't read "love.
Youth
Youth.
It's just the beginning!
Youth!
Adult!
That's a good one!
Encore!
Encore
Rice version
14 is Vivala
Then you've already cleared the youth stage!
Congratulations!
We've got an important song.
What about the rest of the songs?
I don't know.
It's hard to get the glitter.
Where's the glitter going?
Sparkle, sparkle, do it
Sparkle!
Sorekkyu, you should do Vivala or something.
Sorekkyu or
Viva la viva la
Vivala.
M13.
If you do it that way, you have to do it.
if you do it that way...
Oh, I see...
I want to change my nails.
I want to do that.
But I kind of wanted to explain it to you.
That's true.
We have to do it here, too.
But it's the only place to do it.
Study the pretty girl.
So you'll do Sparkles instead?
That's another one.
We'll have to decide on a replacement.
Six patterns.
That's right.
But that's not it, is it?
The 214...
214 and this is A.
A here, B here, C here.
They'll be the same.
Kazushi Yamamoto, let's say we make Fukuoka the same.
The people who came here and here are the same, right? That's right.
So everything changes.
We have to change little by little.
Like A1?
There's A1, A2, and A2.
Let's decide once?
I don't know.
If that's B1.
B1 and A2.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
That's what I'm saying.
Let's say A1 214.
A2 is a pair of shoes.
B2 is 85
B1 is 85
That's right.
that's how it is.
So, the combination
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Done.
What do you want to do there?
Two more A's to go.
As it is now.
If we go around, it's the first one like this.
Round and round... Eddie Buddy.
Oh, and immediately.
Rimto and... OK!
It's good, isn't it?
It looks good.
It fits.
So, where do we go from here?
Doesn't it seem like there's a lot of people coming to this scene?Doesn't it seem like there's a lot of overlap in who comes to this scene?
It seems to cover the same distance.
If we do it in Yokohama or Sendai, the center is pretty good.
If we do it in Osaka or Osaka, but in Tokyo, we'll know.
If we do it here and with girls, it will go around.
Announcement for next time
I'll keep trying.
It's been a while.
These basic
with probability weighing.
what do you think?
Sorry MC
Just this one more thing.
That's right.
What do you think of the overtuner?
What do you think of the overtuner? - I don't know, I think it's just a decoration.
I'm not sure about the concept if you're going to put that in there. I was thinking maybe I could read it, but I'm a little afraid of English.
I'm afraid to read it.
I'm afraid of English.
Or we could split it up, with Yokohama as Ruby and Chie as Moe.
I'll go with 6.
I'll do it like this since it's close to 30 seconds.
What's your career?
I'm confident in my dream.
Up to six.
Okay, Osawa.
That's right.
Then you must be Louis Yokohama.
Kanagawa Prefecture.
If you say so, your birthday's in Longo.
Isn't it?
That's right.
Tokyo
I live in Tokyo.
I came this evening.
I'm here this evening.
You eat a lot of smoked tongue.
Yes.
In this room, it's normal to say it alone.
It's like we all say it here... every time.
Our story is to keep saying it.
When we all say it, we start.
That's the start of each section.
It makes you feel special.
What about when you come with a book?
You mean there's a bigger one?
A little bit bigger
Like red.
Like big in a book.
Someone out in the studio
It would have been better if there was some movement
On the home page
With a red voice.
I'll open it.
Yuka is coming out.
A thought that makes you squeal.
Give me a peck.
I'm embarrassed
A nostalgic, sweet feeling
Ticklish feeling
I have to move and do these things.
Suddenly, a book.
Oh!
What's that?
Open the book and do it like this.
When you talk to a normal person, you do this.
What do you call it?
Open the book.
Or do you open it up and it glows?
Depends on the lighting.
Like a hot light.
On the other hand, how do you retrieve it?
Hold the real thing all the way up.
It's glowing?
How do you retrieve it?
If it glows, you make a recording of it.
If you're going to make a recording...
Read it to people one at a time.
Our story will
Keep echoing.
TelererererererererererererererererererererererererererererereTelererererererererererererererererererererererererererererere
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And then, you know, when you open the book...
Don't you want to close it?
If you leave it open
I don't know...
And then the image...
If I take it out, I'll make it perfect.
The idea of knowing the story of the PAL tour...
The story of the PAL tour.
Pal tour and...
Terererere.
I'm gonna get to know the story of the PAL tour.
So, I'm going to go... now... to the end...
With the PAL Tour
It's something that can be known in the PAL tour.
There is something, isn't there, material?
There is a pattern.
There are patterns.
If there's a pattern, does that mean there's a combo and an automatic?
I, maybe if I don't find it, yeah.
It's open in Yokohama, Sendai or Nagoya, Pirapira.
I'm flipping through it and there,
And the last one?
It's like a pattern.
When did it start?
Wow,
We're getting a song?
The song is out!
The song's out.
Or say something.
Or we'll just flip it around and psycho-regulate.
Or just the "we" part,
We don't always say it, we just say it at the end.
Then, let's do that!
In the middle, come on, let's make the steps come in a regular order.
Let's put on the rhythm and melody that makes the drama comfortable.
Yes, that's it.
Thank you very much!
Yes, it's open.
Se-no!
Our story is a pattern that continues to resonate.
Done!
Yes, the composition and setlist for the Uka Major Debut Spring Tour 2023 have been decided!
Yay!
This is the first time that we have discussed and decided on the setlist together,
It's the first time that we decided on the setlist after a proper discussion amongst ourselves,
But it's going to be a fun show!
It's going to be a fun show!
So please come and join us. Please come and join us.
Thank you very much.
Thank you once, Mr. Sato.